2



Kimberley2609@gmail.com 07404782918





https://uk.linkedin.com/in/kimberley-antao-lal3aal0a

## Qualifications

BSc Computer Science, Smt Parvatibai Chowgule College of Arts and Science, 2016

BCS Foundation in Business Analysis

#### Interests

- Dancing
- Baking

## Profile

My eagerness to learn and improve myself, whilst scrolling through YouTube, watching videos on other people's journey in tech and how they started, I realised the importance of tech in everyone's lives. What intrigued me was there is constant change and development and the lot potential to grow in Tech. I decided to enrol myself in a full stack web development, while working a full-time job and after many sleepless nights, I achieved my "full stack web development diploma" certification.

There were still some technical skills that I wanted to work on, so I enrolled myself in Code Academy. While researching about different fields I came across an opportunity at QA Ltd which ticked both the boxes and this opportunity allowed me to learn new things whilst expanding my knowledge of Tech field.

After completing the Business Analysis 12-week bootcamp with QA, I was deployed at Vivace as a PMO and this is where I got hands on experience on how systems are integrated within the business and the importance of a BA role within it. I worked with key stakeholders, ensuring the clients get value for money and results suiting their needs.

The combination of my experience in retail, my interests, and my keenness to learn is what will make me an asset to the team.

Suggest Process

**Improvements** 

## Skills

#### Stakeholder Engagement **Business** Autonomy, 66.9 **Business Cases** Requirements Engineering Explainer, 87.9 Trusted Technician, 72.6 **Agile and Scrum** Understand Business Cases and Objectives **Design Thinking Working with Processes Technical Process Modelling** Flex. 65.3 Squad Mentality, 45.7 **System Architecture User Experience (UX)** Develop Plans (Scope Growth, 59.7 and Quality) Testing Logical Resolver, 61.3 **Functional** Implementer, 67.7

Strengths Profile

## Day 1 Capabilities



Analyse and Produce Requirements



Monitor and Report on Quality Control Functions



Stakeholder Management



Define and Document Project Scope and Business Requirements



Support Change Management



Assist in Estimations (Cost, Benefit and Time)

# Kimberley Antao

# **Experience**

## Customer Trading Manager - Sainsbury's Ltd - September 2017 to March 2022

- Led a team of up to 20, and drove sales, delivering on all set KPIs
- Engaged with customers and deal with customer complaints to full resolution
- Coached and trained colleagues to meet the standards required.
- Provided a good working place for colleagues.
- Dealt with absences and managed performance
- Prioritized and delegated duties to colleagues.
- Ensured store is trading was in accordance with safe and legal guidelines.
- Took on Store Manager role, overseeing operations during their holidays
- Supervised payroll and dealing with pay queries with close attention to accuracy
- Carried out all cash processes within the store including settling the safe, banking, ordering money and made sure the cash holding was kept within the limit.
- · Identified and ordered all consumables, ensuring smooth operations for all processes in the store.

## Customer Service Assistant – Sainsbury's Ltd – June 2016 to September 2017

- Provided good customer service and achieved 100% score from mystery customers.
- Managed code and quality control.
- Ensured that the tills are functioning smoothly.
- Trained in cash office.
- Carried out lottery and till checks to ensure that the processes were being followed and there was no theft.

## HR Intern - Eka Consultants - November 2015 to December 2015

- Selected candidates for a job role specified by the client.
- Carried out a survey for a new app HireForSure that was soon to be launched

# Kimberley Antao

## **Experience**

## Vivace - PMO-Oct 2022 - 28th April 2023

- As a Project Management Officer, I ensured the ACE processes are followed during several projects. One of the project focused around identifying Parkinson's disease at an early stage.
- Initially when the project started, I ensured I was transparent with all key stakeholders involved and made sure the selection process was fair without being biased.
- Once the supplier was selected, I attended regular meetings with the ACE core (delivery tech leads), and the client team to ensure the client was happy with the progress and changes were made as per client needs.
- One of the major responsibility I had was to make sure I kept track of finances, so the charges were accurate as per sprint.
- I initiated the process of giving access to ACE IT systems, which included making sure that the right people with the correct clearance were added.
- I took charge of scrum ceremonies in the absence of the Delivery lead.

## Vivace - Tech Enabler-April 2023 - Present

- As a Tech Enabler it is my responsibility to ensure that the business process run smoothly and efficiently.
- Tasks ranged from automating business processes which ensures quick results, prompt updates using power automate, researchingon new hardware to improve the office space, creating power apps